Hello friends, I am Unnao Upadhyay, welcome to
all of you on your own YouTube
channel Share Market Analysis. Friends,
here I am going to talk to all of you about
a different topic. The market is
looking quite bullish today. If you
look at the Nifty levels, it will be around 200-
plus. You have seen that the current
position is around 200 10.2. Today's is
180141. On top of that, we are almost
trending down at 80.78 and there is a good
uptrend of 200 points. If you still
look at it, the sector
stocks that I am sharing with you from here have
fallen today, but this is giving you an
opportunity to buy. Today,
even in a good market, these stocks are down, but the
focus is on this sector. We have to keep the focus on these stocks
and this sector is doing well. You must be
well aware of the insurance sector. Now,
talking about the insurance sector, here
I have come with you all after picking some stocks
where I think money can be made.
So let's discuss everything one by one.  Let's move ahead with the
video, but
before that, I have a small request for all of you.
Those who have come to the channel for the first time,
please subscribe to it and press the
notification bell icon so that
every news related to the market reaches you
first. If you like video information like this, then
please like it so that I keep getting
motivation. First of all,
you know what I am picking here.
I had also talked about it in the last video, that is,
LIC i.e. Life Insurance
Corporation of India. If you
want updates on Nifty, then I would like to tell
you this much that near 18000, I
told you in the previous video to buy.
Whoever bought, money has been made, book it and
sit quietly. Now do not do anything. Here,
good support is visible near 18000.
I have a good number of call
riders placed above 1800. The open interest is around ₹2
lakh something. So, if either they
leave their position, that is, they start cutting, then
short covering will take it higher,
but short covering comes when you reach the
level of 18000.  Short cover
means if you want a shortcut to the 1800 level
then you will have to trade Nifty at ₹80000
₹12530 which
looks far from here also so I think if it
trades above then it will exit, if it does not trade then it will go
back down. There is a lot of call
writing also so right now in the rest of the
time that is left, according to me the
market should move between 180,
I don't think anything more can happen than this, let's
see what happens, good and
but the chat pattern is becoming a little positive,
after the correction, Ultra Degi is now going up, so that
looks good, now coming to the
stocks, the first stock I shared with you is
LIC i.e. Life Insurance
Corporation of India, the chart is very strong, I have already
shared the level with you,
you have to keep this top loss at six nine on the bottom
and the first target on the top will be 730, the
second target will be 764,
you can buy this stock for medium term, long term,
medium term or short term
and I would like to say one more thing
which I discuss  I am writing this, you should check it yourself once and
buy it only after that so that your
confidence can be built, it should not be like this, I
said that you have bought it, it should not be so much, it is continuously running, it is
around 90 from the bottom, it
started moving ₹100, it is currently standing at 130
and on the top it has shown you the levels of 140 plus,
I think the
stock will again establish its previous highs, if I
talk a little briefly then you can see a head and shoulder
pattern being formed in the stock, I think right now the
supporter at the bottom is something around 125
and on the top
you will easily
see the stock coming up to 140, so firstly it is nickel, secondly it is GIC, if we
talk about this stock then
you already know this, let's go, I had
recently commented on this stock at 18 and the
target of 200 has come again at 1806,
you are getting an opportunity to buy,
definitely you can buy here also if you want, the
target on the top will still be 200, stay tuned
to this stock also, one more  If I were to
share a stock with you, it would be ICICI
Prudential Life. If we talk about this stock,
you might see a good rally here too.
You should
definitely keep this stock on your radar and keep
looking for buying opportunities in this stock
because this stock looks like one that the
entire sector is doing well at this time. If I
open the ICICI Prudential Life stock here, I can actually see that the
stock chart is
not opening right now, but I
can tell you the levels here. The
stock is trading around 466. It will take
me 2 minutes for it to open. It is
trading here on the phone. It is
down by about 1.5%. But there will definitely be buying opportunities for you. The
stock is
recovering from the bottom and starting to move. If you
look at the weekly candles and even if I
look at the daily candles, it may be down today,
but the chart pattern of the stock is
starting to move up by taking support below. The first level that will
come for you is 480.  There will be a resistance level of 585.00 which is
resistance but the stock will reach there
and if it breaks out then a big wedge can be formed in the stock so
you have to keep this stock on your radar as well. Another
second stock is HDFC
Live. It has already broken out
above 600 but today you are
seeing a connection in the bullish market
because when the market was falling then it is
going up. So you should keep these stocks on your radar
where you are getting
opportunities to buy. Right now the stock chart at 600 is
very interesting. If it recovers a little or goes
down a little, there is a slight increase, if
people book profits then you will find it below
and it will be a good level.
You should buy from this top of 585.70 in the stock,
hence it is preparing to go up to 650.
If you expand the view a little then these are
some stocks which you should keep on
your radar. Hope you understand this video.
Thank you so much for watching this video.